<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>go on Aries notebook</title>
    <link>https://arieszhou.xyz/tags/go/</link>
    <description>Recent content in go on Aries notebook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 22:15:12 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://arieszhou.xyz/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Package - gorm</title>
      <link>https://arieszhou.xyz/post/go-package-gorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 22:15:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arieszhou.xyz/post/go-package-gorm/</guid>
      <description>GORM is a popular Object-Relational Mapping (ORM) package for Go, designed to simplify database operations and improve developer productivity. It provides a robust and expressive API for interacting with various databases, including PostgreSQL, MySQL, SQLite, and more. With GORM, you can focus on your application&amp;rsquo;s logic while it handles the complexities of database management.
Main Usage of GORM:
 Model Definition: GORM allows you to define models, which are Go structs representing database tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Basic - Interface as Parameter to Function</title>
      <link>https://arieszhou.xyz/post/go-basic-interface-as-parameter-to-function/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:50:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arieszhou.xyz/post/go-basic-interface-as-parameter-to-function/</guid>
      <description>https://stackoverflow.com/questions/20314604/go-syntax-and-interface-as-parameter-to-function
 Go uses interfaces for generalization of types. So if you want a function that takes a specific interface you write
1  func MyFunction(t SomeInterface) {...}   Every type that satisfies SomeInterface can be passed to MyFunction.
Now, SomeInterface can look like this:
1 2 3  type SomeInterface interface { SomeFunction() }   To satisfy SomeInterface, the type implementing it must implement SomeFunction().
If you, however, require an empty interface (interface{}) the object does not need to implement any method to be passed to the function:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Package - gorilla mux</title>
      <link>https://arieszhou.xyz/post/go-package-gorilla-mux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 17:00:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arieszhou.xyz/post/go-package-gorilla-mux/</guid>
      <description>Gorilla/mux is a popular package in the Go ecosystem that simplifies routing and URL matching for HTTP services. It offers a rich set of features and allows developers to define custom routes, handle variables, and leverage middleware for enhanced functionality. With gorilla/mux, you can build scalable and maintainable web applications with ease.
Main Usage of gorilla/mux:
 Routing: Gorilla/mux enables you to define powerful and dynamic routes by leveraging patterns, placeholders, and regular expressions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSCode 安装 Go 相关工具失败</title>
      <link>https://arieszhou.xyz/post/vs-code-%E5%AE%89%E8%A3%85-go-%E7%9B%B8%E5%85%B3%E5%B7%A5%E5%85%B7%E5%A4%B1%E8%B4%A5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 17:37:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://arieszhou.xyz/post/vs-code-%E5%AE%89%E8%A3%85-go-%E7%9B%B8%E5%85%B3%E5%B7%A5%E5%85%B7%E5%A4%B1%E8%B4%A5/</guid>
      <description>1 go version go1.19.5 windows/amd64 使用 VS Code 安装 Go 插件后，安装关联工具时，输出内容报如下内容，或错误信息中包含类似 unresponse、timeout 等网络问题相关字</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>